我们继续写我们的content provider。Query将会是
Let's continue coding our content provider. Query will be
content provider需要的方法中最复杂的。
the most complex of the required content provider methods.
我们开始查询操作环节。
We begin with the bones of the query operation.
我们再次使用SURI匹配对象来
We use our SURI matcher object once again to
打开URI类型。这是
switch on the type of URI. This is the
我们填写content provider里
only function where we will have to fill out
每一类型URl的唯一功能。
every type of URI in the content provider. Several
他们中的几个只用来查询。我们将先实现
of them are used for querying only. We'll implement
基础的天气查询。这次查询，我们
the basic weather query first. For this query, we
就要传递所有的参数到
just pass through all of the parameters to the
数据库里。非常简单。我们填写这些参数
database. Pretty simple stuff. Let's fix these parameters so
使他们起作用。所以这里的字符串
they make some sense. So the strings here is
事实上是一个预测。S是一个选择。下一个
actually a projection. S is a selection. The next
数组是选择Args。在上一个字符串里
array is selectionArgs. In the last string is sort
排序顺序来匹配的更好。在这个功能的结尾，
order that matches a lot better. At the bottom
我们给传入这个函数的cursor
of the function, we're going to set the notification
设置一个通知URl
URI for our cursor to the one that was passed into the function.
这会引起cursor注册一个content observer。来监听
This causes the cursor to register a content observer. To watch for changes that
发生在URl和它的任何派生物的变化。通过这些派生物
happen to that URI and any of its descendents. By descendents
我了解了任何URl都通过这一路径。但，我们需要一直测试它。
I mean any URI that begins with this path. But, we still need to test this.